[{"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": ["", "", 3, 2, 1]}], "answers": [5, 4], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": ["", 4, "", 2, 1]}], "answers": [5, 3], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": ["", 4, 3, "", 1]}], "answers": [5, 2], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": ["", 4, 3, 2, ""]}], "answers": [5, 1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": [5, "", "", 2, 1]}], "answers": [4, 3], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": [5, "", 3, "", 1]}], "answers": [4, 2], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": [5, "", 3, 2, ""]}], "answers": [4, 1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": [5, 4, "", "", 1]}], "answers": [3, 2], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": [5, 4, "", 2, ""]}], "answers": [3, 1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "order-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "按顺序填一填", "list": [5, 4, 3, "", ""]}], "answers": [2, 1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-6-05"}]